{
    "id": "afcdb9951116428685fc2fe0f4a5fc68",
    "title": "Determiners Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Can I have ……………………………… fruits?",
            "description": "When we expect yes for an answer, some can be used in questions.",
            "answers": [
                "some",
                "any",
                "few"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. of us was aware of the happenings.",
            "description": "We use plural verbs with all and both. Nobody cannot be used with of us.",
            "answers": [
                "All",
                "Both",
                "None",
                "Nobody"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Who spilled ……………………………. milk on the carpet?",
            "description": "Here the emphasis is not on the quantity hence, much is not used. Many and a cannot be used with uncountable nouns like milk. ",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "many",
                "the",
                "a"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I watched …………………………….. new films last week.",
            "description": "Here many or a few is possible. Many indicates a large number a few indicates a small number. Both are grammatically correct here.",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "much",
                "a lot",
                "a few"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………….. guests are waiting for us.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "The",
                "Any",
                "A"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………. people were injured in the accident.",
            "description": "We can use several or a lot of here. ",
            "answers": [
                "Several",
                "Much",
                "A lot"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t have …………………………… smartphone.",
            "description": "Use a to mean one. ",
            "answers": [
                "the",
                "a",
                "some",
                "an"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She is …………………………….. cleverer than me.",
            "description": "We can use a lot to modify comparative adjectives. ",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "a lot",
                "a lot of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I did hardly ………………………….. work yesterday.",
            "description": "The correct expression is hardly any.",
            "answers": [
                "any",
                "much",
                "many",
                "some"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "There was not …………………………….. room on the bus, so we got off.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "many",
                "any"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………………. of the eggs was in the basket.",
            "description": "Use a plural verb with all and some.",
            "answers": [
                "None",
                "All",
                "Some"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He is …………………………….. university student.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "an",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}